<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Halal or Haram Food E codes</string>
    <string name="actionAbout">About</string>
    <string name="actionAmajadKhan">Amjad Khan List</string>
    <string name="actionRate">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="about">
        E-Numbers represent specific food additives,
        used by the food industry in the manufacture of
        various food products. These E-Numbers have been
        formulated by the European Economic Community (EEC)
        and are universally adopted by the food industry worldwide.\n\nIt is
        known that many E-numbers contain
        unlisted Haram ingredients in them.
        Generally additives derived from animals and insects.\n\nPrior to
        E-numbers were introduced, the name of food ingredients
        were directly provided in the description. So it was easy to avoid
        the foods that contains Haram ingredients like pork fat or suspicious
        animal fat or alcohol. But now it is difficult to determine if a food is
        Halal or Haram just observing the E-numbers.\n\nThis app
        provides information about being Halal or Haram or  Mushbooh (Suspicious)
        of a food based on E-numbers.\n\nMany Muslim
        organizations are working on the issue to find out whether an ingredient is Halal or Haram.
        The study so far has revealed Halal or Haram status of most of the
        ingredients but few are still unknown.\n\nThe data
        were collected from the following links:\n
        https://special.worldofislam.info/Food/numbers.html\n\n
        www.muslimconsumergroup.com/\n\n
        http://www.muslimtents.com/aminahsworld/ecodes.html\n\nAs a
        developer, I state that I’m not responsible or liable for any action based on this information.
    </string>

    <string name="amjadKhanTitle">
        A list by Dr. Amjad Khan
    </string>
    <string name="amjadKhanListDescription">
        An article called \"Are we eating pork?\" has spread in the Internet
        demanding that it is written by Dr. Amjad Khan[ Medical Research Institute, United States],
        but I [the developer] have failed to find the actual
        article but shared posts in many forums by others.\n
        In the article a list of E-numbers has been published that
        contain pork according to study. So the followings are Haram according to the article.\n
    </string>
</resources>
